Finding Aid for Black Mask, 1920-1951.
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1940
  - July 1940: Issue 3 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Someday I'll Kill You" by Edward S. Williams
  - August 1940: Issue 4 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder--For No Reason" by Roger Torrey and "Ten Carats of Lead" by Stewart Sterling
  - September 1940: Issue 5 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Dog Eat Dog" by Robert Reeves and "Pictures for Murder" by W. T. Ballard
  - October 1940: Issue 6 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "C-JAG" by Cornell Woolrich and "Money To Burn" by D. L. Champion
  - November 1940: Issue 7 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "No Sap for Murder" by Carroll John Daly, "Rob and Kill" by Dale Clark, and "You'll Die Laughing" by Norbert Davis
  - December 1940: Issue 8 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Jade Sanctuary" by Earle Stanley Gardner and "Coat of Many Killers" by Stewart Sterling; No back cover.
- 1941
  - January 1941: Issue 9 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Five Minutes for Murder" by Carroll John Daly and "Bomb Heat" by Peter Paige
  - February 1941: Issue 10 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Picture Killer" by John Lawrence, "No Gashes Were Deep" by Roger Torrey and "Skin Game" by Dale Clark
  - March 1941: Issue 11 (Box 13, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "The Flying Hearse" by Robert Reeves and "The Platinum Pig" by Stewart Sterling
  - April 1941: Issue 12 (Box 13, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Dance Macabre" by Robert Reeves, "Vacation with Pay" by D.L. Champion and "Murder Done in Gold" by John Lawrence
  - May 1941: Issue 1 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Once Around the Clock" by George Harmon Coxe
  - June 1941: Issue 2 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "The Cat with a Headache" by Robert Reeves, "Over My Dead Body" by Stewart Sterling and "Split Fee" by D. L. Champion; negative available
  - July 1941: Issue 3 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Calling All Hearses" by H. H. Stinson, "Nobody Loves Cops" by Cleve F. Adams, and "Not in the Script" by W. T. Ballard
  - August 1941: Issue 4 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Death Has My Number" by John K. Butler, "Five Who Killed" by Dale Clark, and "The Sunday That Came on Thursday" by C. P. Donnel, Jr.
  - September 1941: Issue 5 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Milton Luros -- "Iron Cure" by John Lawrence and "Climb Back in Your Coffin" by H. H. Stinson
  - October 1941: Issue 6 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Milton Luros -- "Pick Up the Marbles" by D. L. Champion and "San Quentin Quail" by Dale Clark
  - November 1941: Issue 7 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Don't Bury Me At All" by Stewart Sterling and "Murder is a Swell Idea" by W. T. Ballard
  - December 1941: Issue 8 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Rain Check" by Erle Stanley Gardner
- 1942
  - January 1942: Issue 9 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Milton Luros -- "Bail Bait" by Robert Reeves and "What's Money" by D. L. Champion
  - February 1942: Issue 10 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder, Maestro, Please!" By John Lawrence and "And a Little Child Shall Bleed Them" by C. G. Tahney
  - March 1942: Issue 11 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Kindly Omit Flowers" by Stewart Sterling and "Murder Pays 7 to 1" by D. L. Champion
  - April 1942: Issue 12 (Box 13, Volume 24)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Two Dead Hands" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - May 1942: Issue 1 (Box 13, Volume 25)
  - June 1942: Issue 2 (Box 13, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder in the Red" by George Harmon Coxe and "The Dancing Rats" by Richard Sale
  - July 1942: Issue 3 (Box 13, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Blow the Man Down" by Stewart Sterling and "Three Kills for One" by Cornell Woolrich; No back cover
  - August 1942: Issue 4 (Box 13, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Killer, Can You Spare a Dime?" by D. L. Champion and "Dead Ahead Lies Yesterday" by C. P. Donnel, Jr.
  - September 1942: Issue 5 (Box 13, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Donovan's Brain" by Curt Siodmak
  - October 1942: Issue 6 (Box 13, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder by the Ears" by D. L. Champion and "Blood on the Book" by C. P. Donnel, Jr.
  - November 1942: Issue 7 (Box 14, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Now I Slay Me--" by Dale Clark and "A Taste for Murder" by Robert Reeves
  - December 1942: Issue 8 (Box 14, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder Lays the Keel" by Hugh Pentecost and "Bullets, Back to Back" by Stewart Sterling
- 1943
  - January 1943: Issue 9 (Box 14, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Why Meddle with Murder?" by Merle Constiner and "Blood on the Lens" by George Harmon Coxe
  - February 1943: Issue 10 (Box 14, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Come Out of the Grave!" by D. L. Champion and "Slay as You Go" by Dale Clark
  - March 1943: Issue 11 (Box 14, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "The Incredible Mister Smith" by Erle Stanley Gardner and "Coffin # 3" by Philip Ketchum
  - May 1943: Issue 12 (Box 14, Volume 25)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Mark Hoy's Death Stick" by Walter C. Brown and "Save a Grave for Me" by Frederick C. Davis
  - July 1943: Issue 1 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Dead as a Duck" by Stewart Sterling and "Danger-- Mind at Work!" by C. P. Donnel, Jr.
  - September 1943: Issue 2 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto
  - November 1943: Issue 3 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Kill One, Skip One" by Merle Constiner and "So Red the Ruby" by C. P. Donnel, Jr.
- 1944
  - January 1944: Issue 4 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "A Brain for Sale" by C. G. Tahney and "Murder O' Mine" by Dale Clark
  - March 1944: Issue 5 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder Goes to Market" by Leslie Charters
  - May 1944: Issue 6 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "The Corpse Pays Cash" by D. L. Champion and "The Hound with the Golden Eye" by Merle Constiner
  - July 1944: Issue 7 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder Theme" by Carroll John Daly
  - September 1944: Issue 8 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Cash as Cash Can" by D. L. Champion and "Without Benefit of Camera" by K. M. Knight
  - November 1944: Issue 9 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder A. W. O. L." by Robert Reeves
- 1945
  - January 1945: Issue 10 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "That's Murder for You!" by Dale Clark and "Leave Your Killing Card" by Julius Long
  - March 1945: Issue 11 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Gloria Stoll -- "Murder had a Little Lamb" by Dale Clark
  - May 1945: Issue 12 (Box 14, Volume 26)
    Cover by Gloria Stoll -- "A Noose for Little Nemo" by H. H. Stinson and "The Creeps" by G. T. Fleming-Roberts
  - July 1945: Issue 1 (Box 14, Volume 27)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Spend, Killer, Spend!" by D. L. Champion
  - September 1945: Issue 2 (Box 14, Volume 27)
    Cover by Gloria Stoll -- "Alcoholics Calamitous" by Robert Reeves and "Dead Man's Diary" by Brett Halliday
  - November 1945: Issue 3 (Box 14, Volume 27)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "I'll Be Slaying You" by E. Hoffmann Price and "Your Corpses are Showing" by H. H. Stinson
- 1946
  - January 1946: Issue 4 (Box 14, Volume 27)
    Cover by Gloria Stoll -- "There's Dough in Murder" by C. G. Tahney and "I Ain't Got No Body" by Dale Clark
  - February 1946: Issue 1 (Box 14, Volume 28)
    Cover by Gloria Stoll -- "Deadline for Death" by Thomson Burtis
  - March 1946: Issue 2 (Box 14, Volume 28)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "You're the Crime in My Coffin" by H. H. Stinson
  - May 1946: Issue 3 (Box 15, Volume 28)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Murder by the Carton" by Julius Long
  - July 1946: Issue 4 (Box 15, Volume 28)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Two-Death Parlay" by D. L. Champion
  - September 1946: Issue 1 (Box 15, Volume 29)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Hot-House Homicide" by William Campbell Gault
  - November 1946: Issue 2 (Box 15, Volume 29)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Infernal Revenue" by D. L. Champion and "The Brooklyn Eye" by C. M. Kornbluth
- 1947
  - January 1947: Issue 3 (Box 15, Volume 29)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "The Cold, Cold Ground" by William Campbell Gault
  - March 1947: Issue 4 (Box 15, Volume 29)
    Cover by Albert Drake -- "Dead on Arrival" by Merle Constiner
  - May 1947: Issue 1 (Box 15, Volume 30)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Too Mean to Die" by D. L. Champion
  - July 1947: Issue 2 (Box 15, Volume 30)
    Cover by Malvin Singer -- "The Constant Shadow" by William Campbell Gault
  - September 1947: Issue 3 (Box 15, Volume 30)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Murder Makes the Cock Crow" by Fergus Truslow
  - November 1947: Issue 4 (Box 15, Volume 30)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "The Case of the Sleeping Beauty" by William Campbell Gault
- 1948
  - January 1948: Issue 1 (Box 15, Volume 31)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Red Christmas" by George F. Kull
  - March 1948: Issue 2 (Box 15, Volume 31)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Hanging is Too Good" by Robert Martin
  - May 1948: Issue 3 (Box 15, Volume 31)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "You'll Never Die Rich" by Curtis Cluff
  - July 1948: Issue 4 (Box 15, Volume 31)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Leave Killing to the Cops" by Curtis Cluff
  - September 1948: Issue 1 (Box 15, Volume 32)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Murder is a Pleasure" by H. H. Stinson
  - November 1948: Issue 2 (Box 15, Volume 32)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Overdose of Lead" by Curtis Cluff
- 1949
  - January 1949: Issue 3 (Box 15, Volume 32)
    Cover by Peter Stevens -- "Trouble on Circuit 13" by Robert J. McCain
  - March 1949: Issue 4 (Box 15, Volume 32)
    Cover by unknown. "Flaming Angel" by Frederick C. Davis and "Let's All Swing Together" by Robert Martin
  - May 1949: Issue 1 (Box 15, Volume 33)
    Cover by unknown. "Pardon My Poison Platters" by Fergus Truslow and "Murder in One Syllable" by John D. MacDonald
  - July 1949: Issue 2 (Box 15, Volume 33)
    Cover by unknown. "Richest Man in the Graveyard" by Robert Martin and "Big Shots Die Young" by Richard Deming
  - September 1949: Issue 3 (Box 15, Volume 33)
    Cover by unknown. "Man's Best Friend" by Robert Turner
  - November 1949: Issue 4 (Box 15, Volume 33)
    Cover by unknown. "The 7th Pallbearer" by Robert C. Dennis
- 1950
  - January 1950: Issue 1 (Box 16, Volume 34)
    Cover by unknown. "Dirge in Bolero Time" by Robert Martin
  - May 1950: Issue 3 (Box 16, Volume 34)
    Cover by unknown. "Glitter Street Nightmare" by Robert C. Dennis
  - July 1950: Issue 4 (Box 16, Volume 34)
    Cover by unknown. "Lost in the Shrouds" by Robert Martin and "Jukebox Jungle" by John D. MacDonald
  - November 1950: Issue 2 (Box 16, Volume 35)
    Cover by unknown. "Five O'Clock Shroud" by Richard Deming" and "Hell is What You Make It" by Robert Turner
- 1951
  - January 1951: Issue 3 (Box 16, Volume 35)
  - March 1951: Issue 4 (Box 16, Volume 35)
    Cover by unknown. "For Better or for Death"
  - May 1951: Issue 1 (Box 16, Volume 36)
    Cover by unknown. "Murder in the Ring" by Raoul Whitfield
  - July 1951: Issue 2 (Box 16, Volume 36)
    Cover by unknown. "The Paper Doll" by G. T. Fleming- Roberts